<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ADDICT_TREATMENTS">

        <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>

        <Contributors>
			<Name>Violet Unicorn</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
			
			<!-- ================================================== TREATMENTS ================================================== -->
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_CLOZAPINE</LocID>								
			<Text>Clozapine</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_CLOZAPINE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Clozapine is an atypical antipsychotic medication. It is mainly used for schizophrenia that does not improve following the use of other antipsychotic medications. In those with schizophrenia and schizoaffective disorder it may decrease the rate of suicidal behavior.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ACCEPTANCE_THERAPY</LocID>								
			<Text>Acceptance and Commitment Therapy</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ACCEPTANCE_THERAPY_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Acceptance and Commitment Therapy develops psychological flexibility and is a form of behavioral therapy that combines mindfulness skills with the practice of self-acceptance.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_SUPPORTIVE_PSYCHOTHERAPY</LocID>								
			<Text>Supportive Psychotherapy</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_SUPPORTIVE_PSYCHOTHERAPY_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Supportive psychotherapy is a psychotherapeutic approach that integrates various schools to provide therapeutic support. It includes components from therapeutic schools such as psychodynamic, cognitive-behavioral, and interpersonal conceptual models and techniques.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_EMERGENCY_THIAMINE_INFUSION</LocID>								
			<Text>Emergency Thiamine \nInfusion</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_EMERGENCY_THIAMINE_INFUSION_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Thiamine hydrochloride administered by IV.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BANANA_BAG</LocID>								
			<Text>Banana Bag IV</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BANANA_BAG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>A banana bag (or rally pack) is a bag of IV fluids containing vitamins and minerals. The bags typically contain thiamine, folic acid, and magnesium sulfate, and are usually used to correct nutritional deficiencies or chemical imbalances in the human body. The solution has a yellow color, hence the term "banana bag".</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_METH_ABUSE_REHAB</LocID>								
			<Text>Rehabilitation</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_METH_ABUSE_REHAB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Treating a methamphetamine addiction requires comprehensive courses of detoxification. Treatment involves hospitalisation in a Detox Ward and purging the physical presence of meth from users’ bodies and helping their bodies acclimatize to functioning without meth. Treatment also addresses the psychological damage done by meth, both in terms of rehabilitating the mind, and showing recovering users how they can function and grow in everyday life without the compulsion to seek out meth.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ALCOHOL_ABUSE_REHAB</LocID>								
			<Text>Rehabilitation</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ALCOHOL_ABUSE_REHAB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Treating an alcohol addiction requires comprehensive courses of detoxification. Treatment involves hospitalisation in a Detox Ward and purging the physical presence of alcohol from users’ bodies and helping their bodies acclimatize to functioning without alcohol. Treatment also addresses the psychological damage done by drinking, both in terms of rehabilitating the mind, and showing recovering users how they can function and grow in everyday life without the compulsion to seek out alcohol.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString> <LocID>TRT_HOSPITALIZATION_DETOX</LocID>
			<Text>Detox hospitalization </Text>  
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString> <LocID>TRT_HOSPITALIZATION_DETOX_DESC</LocID> 
            <Text>Hospitalize the patient at a detox ward. \n\nRequired room: Detox ward</Text>  
        	</GameDBLocalizedString>

        	<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BETHANECHOL</LocID>								
			<Text>Bethanechol</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BETHANECHOL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Bethanechol is used to treat certain bladder problems such as the inability to urinate or empty the bladder completely due to certain causes (e.g., surgery, bladder muscle problems). It works by helping the bladder muscle to squeeze better, thereby improving the ability to urinate. Bethanechol may also be used to treat heartburn. It works by helping the stomach muscles move food down out of the stomach faster and by increasing the strength of the muscle between the esophagus and stomach (lower esophageal sphincter). This helps prevent food/acid in the stomach from rising back into the esophagus.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ACETAZOLAMIDE</LocID>								
			<Text>Acetazolamide</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_ACETAZOLAMIDE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Acetazolamide is a medication used to treat glaucoma, epilepsy, altitude sickness, periodic paralysis, idiopathic intracranial hypertension (raised brain pressure of unclear cause), and heart failure.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BACLOFEN</LocID>								
			<Text>Baclofen</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRT_VIO_BACLOFEN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					
			<Text>Baclofen is used to treat muscle spasms caused by certain conditions (such as multiple sclerosis, involuntary eye movement, spinal cord injury/disease). It works by helping to relax the muscles.</Text>	
			</GameDBLocalizedString>

			</LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>